# Dang Pham

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER-**



# • CONTACT

108/40/28 LE VAN LUONG

Phone: +84 935 245 556
Email: hello@pnhd.design
Website: http://pnhd.design

Facebook: phamnhathaidan

Behance: five3105 LinkedIn: Đăng Phạm

#### • SKILLS

#### Professional:

- Graphic Design
- UI Design
- Motion Graphic
- Photography

## Software:

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Adohe After Effects

### • LANGUAGE

Vietnamese
 Native



• English
Intermediate



#### SUMMERY

Hello! I'm Dang Pham. I am a Senior Graphic Designer from Da Lat City, who have been around advertising agencies for more than four years. I've studied at FPT Arena Multimedia in Ho Chi Minh city, where I spend most of my time learning and working on awesome projects and currently studying Motion Graphics at Red Cat Academy and Motion Design School.

### • EDUCATION

# Tay Son High School

2008-2010

### FPT Arena Multimedia

2014-2016

#### **Red Cat Academy**

2019 - Presen

### **Motion Design School**

2019 - Present

# • WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer 2016-2017

Mat Bao Corporation / 54 C1, District Tan Binh, HCM City

Design banner/website and other stuff for company.

### Graphic Designer 2017-2019

AA Distribution / 61A-63A Vo Van Tan, District 3, HCM City

Design banner/Shop in Shop layout on ecommerce channels (Tiki, Lazada Sendo Shopee Adayroi)

**UI Designer** 8/2019-11/2019

Epsilo.io / 61A-63A Vo Van Tan, District 3, HCM City

Design website layout, animation for The Scale Group, Epsilo and other multimedia for company